hi folks welcome back so this is Matt
大家好，欢迎回来，这是马特
Jackson and we're talking now about
杰克逊，我们现在谈论的是
defining games and we'll work through
定义游戏，我们将继续努力
some basic definitions of the key
密钥的一些基本定义
ingredients in games so let's take a
游戏中的成分，所以让我们来
look at some of those so obviously one
看那些很明显的那些
one of the most obvious ones is the
最明显的一个是
players in the game so who's making the
游戏中的玩家，谁在创造
decisions are they people are we talking
决定是他们在说我们吗
about governments negotiating over trade
关于政府就贸易进行谈判
agreements are we talking about
我们在谈论协议
companies choosing their strategies for
公司为其选择策略
developing new products do we want to
开发我们想要的新产品
get down to the point of modeling people
深入到建模人的地步
within a firm as opposed to the company
在公司内部而不是公司内部
as a whole so this whole there's a whole
作为一个整体，所以整个
series of questions about how we're
关于我们如何的一系列问题
going to choose the players but there
要选择球员，但在那里
they're going to be the central decision
他们将成为中心决策
makers and what we're doing next we have
制造商以及我们下一步要做的事情
to decide how we're going to model the
决定我们如何建模
action so what can play what actions can
行动，所以可以发挥什么作用
players actually take so when we later
玩家实际上选择了
on in the course we'll be looking at
在课程中，我们将继续研究
auctions
拍卖会
they'll have bids so they can enter a
他们将有出价，以便他们可以输入
number of bids when we're talking about
我们谈论的竞标数量
bargaining they might be deciding
讨价还价他们可能会决定
whether or not to strike when we're
我们是否要罢工
thinking about investing it could be
考虑投资它可能是
that an investor is deciding how much of
投资者在决定多少
a stock to buy or sell when to buy or
何时购买或出售的股票
sell it how they should react to other
卖给他们他们应该如何回应其他人
people in the market how they should be
市场中的人们应该如何
conditioning their decisions on prices
以价格决定他们的决定
when we're thinking about voters how do
当我们在考虑选民时
they vote so there's going to be a whole
他们投票，所以将有一个整体
series of actions and we'll want to be
一系列的动作，我们希望成为
careful in making sure that we have the
小心确保我们拥有
essential actions modeled finally
最终模仿的基本行动
payoffs
收益
so what's motivating the players do they
所以激励球员的是他们
care simply about some sort of profit do
只是在乎某种利润
they care about other players so how are
他们关心其他球员，所以
they receiving utility as a function of
他们收到的效用是
what what the actions lead to in the
这些动作会导致什么
context of the game so there's basically
游戏的背景，所以基本上
two standard representations of games
游戏的两种标准表示形式
one is what's known as the normal form
一种是普通形式
and that's what we'll be starting with
这就是我们要开始的
in the course and what it does is it
在课程中，它是做什么的
it's a very simple and stark
这是非常简单而鲜明的
representation of a game so it lists
游戏的表示形式，因此它列出了
what payoffs players get as a fun
玩家会从中获得什么收益
of their actions normally it's it's
通常是他们的行为
thought of as as if players are moving
好像玩家在移动
simultaneously but strategies and we'll
同时但战略，我们将
talk about this in more detail can
详细讨论一下可以
encode many things so the other
编码很多东西，其他
alternative representation is what's
替代表示是什么
known as the extensive form and that
被称为广泛形式
includes more explicit timing in the
包括更明确的时间安排
game so who moves at what at what point
游戏，以便谁在什么时候移动
in time so that's going to be
及时，这将是
represented often as a tree so for
通常代表一棵树
instance in chess one player moves first
在国际象棋中，一个玩家先移动
the white player generally moves first
白人球员通常先走
and the black player can see the move by
黑人玩家可以看到
the other player react to that and and
另一个玩家对此做出反应，并且
so forth so that's going to be better
等等，这样会更好
represented as a tree then then in
表示为一棵树，然后
normal form so it keeps track of also
正常形式，所以它也跟踪
what players know when they move so even
玩家知道什么时候他们移动
in poker somebody moves first they make
在扑克中，有人先移动
a bet but the other player only sees the
下注，但其他玩家只看到
bet and not necessarily the cards that
下注，不一定是
the other player sees so in some cases
在某些情况下，其他玩家看到了
we'll have sequential games where
我们将有连续游戏
players will have different information
玩家会有不同的信息
at different points in time and we'll
在不同的时间点，我们将
we'll want to talk about modeling that
我们将要讨论建模
explicitly - so we're going to start out
明确地-因此我们将开始
with the normal form and then we'll move
以正常形式，然后我们将移动
later in the course to the extensive
在课程的后期向广泛
form and we'll talk about the
表格，我们将讨论
relationship between these two and more
这两个和更多之间的关系
detail
详情
okay so normal form games what are the
好吧，那么普通的形式游戏是什么
key ingredients again players so we're
关键因素再次成为球员，所以我们
going to have generally we're going to
通常我们要
think of finite sets of players so 1
想想有限的玩家集合，所以1
through n little n will represent the
通过n小n将代表
set of players generally will index
一组球员一般都会索引
these things by an eye so we'll use a
这些东西，所以我们将使用
little eye to represent the the generic
小眼睛代表通用
player the action set for 4 players will
玩家为4位玩家设定的动作将
represent by a sub eye ok so we'll let
用肉眼代表，好吧，让我们
that represent the actions of player eye
代表玩家视线的动作
and then we'll talk about profiles of
然后我们将讨论
actions which will just be a list of
动作将仅是
what every player is doing so for
每个玩家都在做什么
instance are they just deciding to
例如，他们只是决定
cooperate or not to cooperate with other
合作或不合作
players for instance in a prisoner's
例如囚犯的玩家
dilemma that will
将会陷入的困境
about utility function is then a payoff
关于效用函数是一个回报
function which indicates as a function
表示功能的功能
of all the actions that are played
播放的所有动作中
what's the payoff for the different
不同的收益是什么
players so for each player I we end up
玩家，所以我最终每位玩家
with a function which tells us how they
带有告诉我们他们如何
evaluate outcomes of the game and again
评估游戏结果
how they evaluate these things could
他们如何评估这些事情
could it caps late many things and it's
它可以限制很多事情吗，这是
going to be very important to make sure
非常重要的是要确保
that we're getting the right
我们做对了
representation of what really motivates
真正激励的代表
people okay so often when we when we
人们经常这样，当我们当我们
represent non form games a very simple
代表非形式游戏非常简单
way of doing that is just in the matrix
这样做的方式只是在矩阵中
representation so let's just look at
表示法，让我们来看看
this the most standard representation of
这是最标准的表示
very simple games writing a two-player
两个人玩的非常简单的游戏
game as a matrix so we'll have one
游戏作为矩阵，所以我们将有一个
player 1 will be the row player player 2
玩家1将成为行玩家2
will have via column player so they're
将通过列播放器，所以他们
going to choose actions that will be
选择要采取的行动
represented in the column of the matrix
在矩阵列中表示
and the cells inside the cells will then
然后细胞内的细胞将
represent the payoffs so for instance
代表收益，例如
the TCP back off game that was talked
讨论过的TCP后退游戏
about in the earlier video can be
在较早的视频中可以
written as a matrix as follows so the
写成如下矩阵
row player player one can choose either
行播放器玩家可以选择
C or D so this is player 1s choice then
C或D，所以这是玩家1的选择
we known as the role player this is
我们被称为角色扮演者
player two's the column player and they
玩家二是专栏玩家，他们
represent the the choices that they have
代表他们的选择
and an inside the cells are the payoffs
细胞内部是收益
to the different players so if player
给不同的玩家，所以如果玩家
one cooperates and player two cooperates
一合作，二合作
then these are the payoffs to the two
那么这就是两者的收益
players the first payoff player one
玩家第一位回报玩家
second playoff player two so this is
第二个季后赛球员，所以这是
going to the column player this one's
去专栏玩家这个
going to the row player okay then we end
转到行播放器好，然后我们结束
up you know for instance if the row
最多，例如，如果该行
player chooses D and the column player
玩家选择D，而列玩家
chooses C then we end up with a payoff
选择C，然后我们得到回报
here of zero
零这里
the Rope layer and -4 to the column
绳索层和-4列
player so the matrix is a very simple
播放器，因此矩阵非常简单
way of representing all of the basic
代表所有基本的方式
elements of the normal form game
普通形式游戏的要素
visually so that we can actually keep
视觉上，以便我们实际上可以保持
track of exactly what the strategic
准确地追踪战略
interaction is and what players would
互动是什么，玩家会怎样
like to do as a function of the game ok
喜欢做游戏的功能好吗
let's talk about another game that we
让我们谈谈我们的另一款游戏
won't be able to write down in such a
这样的话将无法写下
simple form so let's think of a large
简单的形式，让我们想一想
collective action game so for instance
集体动作游戏，例如
whether or not a population wants to
人口是否想要
revolt against this government so here
反抗这个政府，所以在这里
we have many more players so let's
我们还有更多的球员，所以让我们
imagine that we have a population of 10
想象我们有10个人
million players so we're not obviously
百万玩家，所以我们不是很明显
not going to be able to write that down
无法将其写下来
as a as a matrix on our screen so we can
作为屏幕上的矩阵，因此我们可以
do that more abstractly but we'll have
可以更抽象地做，但是我们有
10 million players whether they they
1000万玩家，无论他们
what are their actions here let's keep
他们在这里做什么？
it very simple so they have a choice
非常简单，所以他们可以选择
here of either revolting or not so their
这里要么反抗，要么不反抗
action set is just binary two choices
操作集只是二进制的两个选择
then the payoffs are going to be the
那么收益将是
critical thing in this game what happens
在这个游戏中关键的事情发生了什么
well let's say that in order for revolt
好吧，为了反抗
to be successful you need at least two
要成功，您至少需要两个
million people to participate so in this
百万人参加
particular stylized example what do we
特定的程式化示例
end up with then we can represent a
最后我们可以代表一个
successful revolt as the player getting
随着玩家获得成功反叛
a payoff of 1 so UI of the action
收益为1，因此操作的用户界面
profile a is equal to 1 if the number of
如果a的数量等于1
people here the number of players J such
这里的人数
that they picked to revolt the number of
他们选择反抗的数量
this is at least 2 million so if we end
这至少是200万，所以如果我们结束
up with at least 2 million people
至少有200万人
revolting then player I gets 1 and note
令人反感的玩家我得到1并注意
here that this is true regardless of
在这里，这是真的，无论
whether I is one of the revolt
我是否是叛乱之一
participants so this is a game where you
参与者，所以这是一个游戏
care about the end outcome not
不在乎最终结果
necessarily getting utility out of the
必然会从中获得效用
participation we could change this and
参与，我们可以改变这一点，
have people get enjoyment out of the
让人们从中获得乐趣
participation or
参与或
have costs of the participation directly
直接承担参加费用
as well
以及
okay so what's what happens if the if
好吧，如果
things fail here if we end up with less
如果我们少吃点东西，事情就会失败
than two million then it depends on
超过两百万则取决于
whether you were a participant in the
您是否参加了
revolt or not so if you if player I was
反叛与否，如果你是我的话
a participant in the revolt and it fails
叛乱的参与者而失败
then they get a payoff of negative one
然后他们得到负数的回报
so this could be in a situation where
所以这可能是在
they're punished by the government or
他们受到政府的惩罚或
face some other kinds of sanctions and
面临其他制裁
they get a payoff of zero if the revolts
如果起义，他们得到的回报为零
not successful and they didn't
不成功，他们没有
participate so they weren't one of the
参加，所以他们不是其中之一
people that was actually revolting now
现在真正反抗的人
obviously this is very stylized but what
显然，这是非常风格化的，但是
it does capture is that players have to
它确实捕获了玩家必须
strategically analyze and predict what
战略性地分析和预测什么
other players are going to do and their
其他玩家将要做的
payoffs depend not only on what they're
收益不仅取决于它们的价值
doing right so here we have a situation
做得好，所以在这里我们有一个情况
where player i's payoff depends on
我的收益来源取决于
whether they revolt or not but it also
他们是否反抗，但也
depends on what other players are doing
取决于其他玩家在做什么
and it can depend in fairly complicated
这可能取决于相当复杂的
ways on what all the players in the game
游戏中所有玩家的方式
are doing okay so just in summary in
一切正常，所以在总结中
defining games we have two different
定义游戏我们有两种不同
forms the normal form and extensive form
形成正常形式和广义形式
for now we're starting with the normal
现在我们从普通的
form critical ingredients players
形成关键成分的参与者
actions and payoffs later when we get to
行动和回报以后，当我们到达
the extension form that's going to bring
将会带来的扩展形式
in timing information and so forth so
在时间信息等方面
extra things that will account for more
多余的东西会占更多
detailed representations of the
的详细表示
strategic interaction by players
玩家之间的战略互动